Born in fear...baptized in blood...his ultimate challenge was survival
Order of the Eagle is a adventure, action film directed by Thomas Baldwin.
A teenage Eagle Scout accidentally discovers the lost plans for America's Star Wars missile defense
program and soon becomes a target for a squad of ruthless industrial espionage hit men.
Mr. Quill, played by Frank Stallone Jr..
John Billings, played by William Zipp.
Monica (as Jil Foor), played by Jill Foor.
Freddie, played by Perry Hill.
Greg, played by Casey Hirsch.
Leo, played by David Roger Harris.
Kickboxer is a 1989 American martial arts film directed by
David Worth and starring Jean-Claude Van Damme.
Former world kickboxing champion Dennis Alexio is also featured.
The plot revolves around Kurt Sloane (Van Damme) seeking revenge on the fearsome kickboxing
champion Tong Po (Michel Qissi) who paralyzed his brother Eric Sloane (Dennis Alexio).
The film is regarded as the first movie to bring Muay Thai
(Thai kickboxing) to a global audience.
Produced by Kings Road Entertainment and released by The Cannon Group, Inc.
on September 8, 1989, it grossed $50 million on a budget of $2.7 million.
It spawned several sequels.